http://www.amtote.com/home/terms-use

Skip to main content
Skip to main content
Terms of Use
Body
Please read these Terms of Use before using this Web site. By using this Web site you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions of use. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, please do NOT use this Web site. If for any reason you are not satisfied with this Web site, your sole exclusive remedy is to stop using this Web site.
AmTote International, Inc. ("AmTote") reserves the right to modify these Terms of Use at any time. Any changes to the Terms of Use shall become effective when they are posted on this Web site.
Intellectual Property
Copyright
The materials on this Web site, including but not limited to the text, graphics, images, information and layout, are protected by United States and International Copyright laws. You may not reproduce, distribute, transmit, display, prepare derivative works, or perform any copyrighted material provided on the AmTote Web site without the prior written consent of AmTote, except as provided below:
The materials may be used for non-commercial, internal informational purposes only.
Any copy of these materials or any portion thereof must not be modified and must retain all copyright and other notices, and must not be posted on any network computer or broadcast in any media.
AmTote may revoke or modify any of the foregoing rights at any time.
Trademark
Spectrum® , TrackBase® , AmTote® , VoiceBet® , BingoBet® , BetMate® , HandiBet® , PariMAX™, MBet™ FileBet™; and BetWizard® are registered trademarks/service marks of AmTote International, Inc. All other trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos and emblems displayed on this Web site are the trademarks of their respective owners and have been used with their permission.
Please note that any product, process or technology described in these materials may also be the subject of other intellectual property rights reserved by AmTote and/or its subsidiaries and are not licensed hereunder.
Unsolicited Idea/Invention Submission Policy
Occasionally, AmTote International, Inc. ("AmTote") is contacted by outside individuals who are interested in submitting unsolicited inventions, ideas and/or suggestions in all stages of development for AmTote to consider. For more information on AmTote's policy regarding the submission of unsolicited ideas/inventions and the required procedures for making such a submission please see AmTote's Unsolicited Idea/Invention Submission Policy.
Disclaimers and Limitation of Liability
AMTOTE TAKES GREAT CARE TO ENSURE THAT THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THIS WEB SITE IS ACCURATE AND UP TO DATE. THIS INFORMATION COULD CONTAIN TECHNICAL INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS, AND INFORMATION MAY BE CHANGED, UPDATED AND/OR DELETED AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE. AMTOTE MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE PRODUCTS AND/OR THE PROGRAMS DESCRIBED IN THIS MATERIAL AT ANY TIME. HOWEVER, THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THIS WEB SITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU "AS IS," FOR YOUR INFORMATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY, WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANT OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, OR SATISFACTORY QUALITY. PLEASE NOTE THAT SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES, SO THE ABOVE EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
ADDITIONALLY, AMTOTE MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER ABOUT ANY OTHER WEB SITE WHICH YOU MAY CHOOSE TO ACCESS THROUGH THIS WEB SITE. LINKS PROVIDED BY AMTOTE TO SUCH WEB SITES ARE PROVIDED SOLELY FOR YOUR CONVENIENCE AND SHOULD NOT BE DEEMED TO IMPLY THAT AMTOTE ENDORSES THOSE WEB SITES OR ANY CONTENT CONTAINED THEREIN. IN NO EVENT WILL AMTOTE INTERNATIONAL, INC. BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY OR OTHER TYPES OF CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY TYPE WHATSOEVER RELATING TO OR ARISING FROM THIS WEB SITE OR ANY USE OF THIS WEB SITE OR ANY OTHER HYPERLINKED WEB SITE INCLUDING SPECIFICALLY, BUT NOT EXCLUSIVELY, ANY LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF GOOD WILL, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF DATA, EVEN IF AMTOTE IS EXPRESSLY ADVISED ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS EXCLUSION AND WAIVER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY AND ALL CAUSES OF ACTION, WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, WARRANTY, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LETHAL THEORY.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless AmTote International, Inc. and its affiliates for any claims, losses, or damages, including legal fees, resulting form your violation of these terms, and to fully cooperate with AmTote and its affiliates in the defense of any such claims.
Choice of Law/Forum Selection
You agree that these terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Maryland, any claims arising under these terms will be subject to the laws of the State of Maryland, and you consent to personal jurisdiction and venue in the courts of the State of Maryland.
AmTote DOES NOT want to receive any confidential or proprietary information from you through its Web site. Any information that AmTote receives through its Web site, other than your personally identifiable information, as explained in AmTote's Privacy Policy, will be deemed to be NON-CONFIDENTIAL. By transmitting any information to AmTote via this Web site or otherwise through electronic means, you grant to AmTote an unrestricted, irrevocable license to use, sub-license, reproduce, display, modify, perform, transmit and distribute such information, and AmTote is free to use the information, including any ideas, know-how, concepts or techniques contained therein free of charge and for any purpose whatsoever.
This Web site may contain other proprietary notices and conditions of use, the terms of which must also be observed and followed.
PRIVACY POLICY
AmTote respects your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we may collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Web site.
Collection of Visitor Information
AmTote does not collect any personally identifiable information (such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number or email address) from you unless you voluntarily choose to disclose such information to us either through our Web site or through email correspondence. We will collect general information such as the type of Internet browser you use, the files that you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information. This information is collected so that we may improve our Web site in order to better meet your needs.
Use of Cookies
Cookies are small bits of information that a Web site places on the user's hard drive that are often used to collect information about how the Web site is used. AmTote currently does not utilize Internet cookies, but may do so in the future.
Use of Information
Information collected by AmTote is used solely for the purposes of compiling usage statistics regarding our Web site, responding to visitor inquiries, and analyzing visitor preferences regarding our services and products. We will not share, sell, rent or give away the information provided to use by site visitors, except as permitted or required by law or if pertinent judicial or governmental investigations require the release of your personally identifiable information. However, visitor information may be shared or sold to any successor to or purchaser of part or all of the assets of the business.
Children's Online Privacy Protection
AmTote appreciates the importance of protecting children's privacy, especially in today's online environment. This Web site is not intentionally designed for or directed toward children under the age of 16, and we will not intentionally collect or maintain any information about anyone under the age of 16 without permission of the child's parent or legal guardian. Children under the age of 16 should not submit personally identifiable information without the explicit permission of their parent or legal guardian. Where appropriate, AmTote will instruct children not to submit personally identifiable information. In the event that your child has submitted personally identifiable information and you would like to request that such information be removed, you may do so at any time and AmTote will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Such requests can be made by contacting us at webmaster@amtote.com.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Web site may contain links to other Web sites which are neither owned nor controlled by AmTote. In the event that you visit these sites, we recommend that you take the time to read each of their independent Privacy Policies, as AmTote does not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or Privacy Policies of those Web sites.
AmTote permits links to content on AmTote's Web site only with the express written permission of an officer of AmTote who is authorized to grant such permission. Such linking should not suggest that AmTote promotes or endorses any third party causes, ideas, Web sites, products or services. Additionally, the linking should not use AmTote content for any inappropriate purposes, commercial or otherwise. AmTote reserves the right to withdraw its permission for any link at any time.
AmTote does not permit framing of its Web site.
Changes in the Privacy Policy
AmTote reserves the right to modify or change its Privacy Policy at any time. We will promptly reflect any such modifications or changes in these Web pages. Please check our Privacy Policy regularly.
Contact Us
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please send an email to webmaster@amtote.com.
Terms Of Use
| Submission Policy | Site Map
© Copyright 2001-2017 AmTote International, Inc. All rights reserved. Usage of this website is an automatic acceptance of our Terms Of Use Policy.
All unsolicited intellectual property submissions to AmTote are covered under our Submission policy. "AmTote" is a registered trademark of AmTote International, Inc.
Home
Company
About Us
Customers
Meet The Team
Senior Management Team
Sales Team
Departments
Why PariMAX?
Games Library
PariMAX™ FAQ
Contact Us
Login
